<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Le Wagon Selected Posts</title>
<link>https://blog.lewagon.com/</link>
<description>Custom RSS feed based on selected URLs</description>
<item>
<title>Top 5 data visualization tools</title>
<link>https://blog.lewagon.com/skills/top-5-data-visualization-tools/</link>
<description>&lt;p&gt;Struggling to make data impactful? Let me show you how AI data visualization tools and big data visualization tools transform numbers into compelling visuals. These tools make interactive data visualization a breeze and help you tell stories that drive results.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;L’article &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com/skills/top-5-data-visualization-tools/&quot;&gt;Top 5 data visualization tools&lt;/a&gt; est apparu en premier sur &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com&quot;&gt;Blog Le Wagon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 15:52:34 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>How to launch a successful AI startup/ business?</title>
<link>https://blog.lewagon.com/skills/how-to-launch-a-successful-ai-startup-business/</link>
<description>&lt;p&gt;So, you’re thinking of starting an AI business? Let’s dive into the essential steps to launch successfully—identifying market opportunities, defining your niche, and using AI-powered GTM strategies. I’ll walk you through it all, from building a team to creating scalable AI solutions that grow with your business.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;L’article &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com/skills/how-to-launch-a-successful-ai-startup-business/&quot;&gt;How to launch a successful AI startup/ business?&lt;/a&gt; est apparu en premier sur &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com&quot;&gt;Blog Le Wagon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 16:03:42 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Entrepreneurship content: how to leverage AI for your startup?</title>
<link>https://blog.lewagon.com/skills/entrepreneurship-content-how-to-leverage-ai-for-your-startup/</link>
<description>&lt;p&gt;Building your startup’s future?... Learn how AI-driven tools for marketing, predictive analytics, and personalized customer experiences can transform your business. It’s all about making smarter, data-driven decisions that drive growth and innovation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;L’article &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com/skills/entrepreneurship-content-how-to-leverage-ai-for-your-startup/&quot;&gt;Entrepreneurship content: how to leverage AI for your startup?&lt;/a&gt; est apparu en premier sur &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com&quot;&gt;Blog Le Wagon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 14:50:16 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Rise of no-code/ low-code platforms: how developers can adapt in 2025</title>
<link>https://blog.lewagon.com/skills/rise-of-no-code-low-code-platforms-how-developers-can-adapt-in-2025/</link>
<description>&lt;p&gt;No-code and low-code platforms are reshaping web development and the future roles of developers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;L’article &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com/skills/rise-of-no-code-low-code-platforms-how-developers-can-adapt-in-2025/&quot;&gt;Rise of no-code/ low-code platforms: how developers can adapt in 2025&lt;/a&gt; est apparu en premier sur &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com&quot;&gt;Blog Le Wagon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 14:54:59 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>pandas &amp; PySpark</title>
<link>https://blog.lewagon.com/skills/pandas-pyspark/</link>
<description>&lt;p&gt;Explore strategies for seamlessly integrating pandas and PySpark to maximize performance and efficiency. This article dives into leveraging the pandas API on Spark and harnessing the power of pandas UDFs, demonstrating how to combine the simplicity and flexibility of pandas with the scalability of PySpark. Learn how these tools complement each other to enable efficient, large-scale data processing without compromising usability or ease of implementation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;L’article &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com/skills/pandas-pyspark/&quot;&gt;pandas &amp;#038; PySpark&lt;/a&gt; est apparu en premier sur &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com&quot;&gt;Blog Le Wagon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 15:42:23 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Emerging data science &amp; AI trends for 2025</title>
<link>https://blog.lewagon.com/skills/emerging-data-science-ai-trends-for-2025/</link>
<description>&lt;p&gt;In 2025, AI and data are reshaping industries, with 46.4% of companies already realizing significant value from their investments. Key trends like generative AI, agentic AI, and responsible AI practices are leading the charge in innovation, while organizations focus on managing unstructured data, expanding leadership roles such as CDOs and CAIOs, and addressing cultural and talent challenges. These developments reflect the strategic, human-centered approach necessary for AI to drive sustainable growth and transformation in businesses across industries.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;L’article &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com/skills/emerging-data-science-ai-trends-for-2025/&quot;&gt;Emerging data science &amp;#038; AI trends for 2025&lt;/a&gt; est apparu en premier sur &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com&quot;&gt;Blog Le Wagon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 16:31:12 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
