<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Le Wagon News Only</title>
<link>https://blog.lewagon.com/news/</link>
<description>Filtered feed for /news/ posts only</description>
<item>
<title>What are the financing and discount options for Le Wagon Tokyo bootcamps in 2026?</title>
<link>https://blog.lewagon.com/news/financing-options-tokyo/</link>
<description>&lt;p&gt;Le Wagon Tokyo offers multiple financial aid, scholarships, and payment plans for students enrolling in our AI Software nd Data Science &amp;#038; AI bootcamps. Below are the main options available, along with eligibility requirements and application procedures.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;L’article &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com/news/financing-options-tokyo/&quot;&gt;What are the financing and discount options for Le Wagon Tokyo bootcamps in 2026?&lt;/a&gt; est apparu en premier sur &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com&quot;&gt;Blog Le Wagon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 02:12:56 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Update 2026: HelloWork subsidy with Le Wagon Tokyo</title>
<link>https://blog.lewagon.com/news/tokyo-hellowork-subsidy/</link>
<description>&lt;p&gt;Since 2021, Le Wagon Tokyo bootcamps are eligible for the HelloWork subsidy under the Ministry of Health, Labour and Welfare’s Specialized Practice Education and Training Benefits Program (専門実践教育訓練給付金). This means that eligible students can receive up to 70% of their tuition reimbursed, making career transitions into tech more accessible than ever.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;L’article &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com/news/tokyo-hellowork-subsidy/&quot;&gt;Update 2026: HelloWork subsidy with Le Wagon Tokyo&lt;/a&gt; est apparu en premier sur &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com&quot;&gt;Blog Le Wagon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Navigating the Canadian tech job market</title>
<link>https://blog.lewagon.com/news/navigating-the-canadian-tech-job-market/</link>
<description>&lt;p&gt;Le Wagon Canada, in collaboration with rhum, has released a white paper on Canada’s job market, focusing on tech and AI skills. It highlights what businesses need, the skills most in demand, and the challenges created by a fast-changing, AI-driven market.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;L’article &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com/news/navigating-the-canadian-tech-job-market/&quot;&gt;Navigating the Canadian tech job market&lt;/a&gt; est apparu en premier sur &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com&quot;&gt;Blog Le Wagon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 08:18:28 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Why Non-Coders Are Falling Behind in the AI Era</title>
<link>https://blog.lewagon.com/news/why-non-coders-are-falling-behind-in-the-ai-era/</link>
<description>&lt;p&gt;Today, everyone is using AI to be more efficient, but are they using it to be more effective? Why are the most effective AI users people with programming skills? &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;L’article &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com/news/why-non-coders-are-falling-behind-in-the-ai-era/&quot;&gt;Why Non-Coders Are Falling Behind in the AI Era&lt;/a&gt; est apparu en premier sur &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com&quot;&gt;Blog Le Wagon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 03:19:11 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Inside Kitt: the platform that powers your bootcamp journey</title>
<link>https://blog.lewagon.com/news/inside-kitt-the-platform-that-powers-your-bootcamp-journey/</link>
<description>&lt;p&gt;More than just a course platform, Kitt is the intelligent learning environment behind Le Wagon’s global bootcamps. In this article, we explore the student-facing features that make Kitt a key reason our learners succeed—and why it sets Le Wagon apart from other tech schools.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;L’article &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com/news/inside-kitt-the-platform-that-powers-your-bootcamp-journey/&quot;&gt;Inside Kitt: the platform that powers your bootcamp journey&lt;/a&gt; est apparu en premier sur &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com&quot;&gt;Blog Le Wagon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:46:18 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>AgTech: data for agriculture</title>
<link>https://blog.lewagon.com/news/agtech-data-for-agriculture/</link>
<description>&lt;p&gt;During an event at the Montréal campus, we brought together agtech experts to discuss the use of data in agriculture. Around the table were Colline Blanc, Data Scientist, Justin Hogue and John Lan, both R&amp;#038;D Scientists at ChrysaLabs. The discussion was hosted by Hugo Dupuis, Program Director at Zone Agtech.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;L’article &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com/news/agtech-data-for-agriculture/&quot;&gt;AgTech: data for agriculture&lt;/a&gt; est apparu en premier sur &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com&quot;&gt;Blog Le Wagon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 16:08:33 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Le Wagon Tokyo campus reaches 1,000 graduates!</title>
<link>https://blog.lewagon.com/news/le-wagon-tokyo-coding-bootcamp-1000-graduates/</link>
<description>&lt;p&gt;After exactly 8 years, our Tokyo campus is celebrating a huge milestone: we&#x27;ve reached 1,000 Full-Stack Web Development and Data Science &amp;#038; AI graduates! From the number of nationalities to age ranges, let&#x27;s discover more about them 👀&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;L’article &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com/news/le-wagon-tokyo-coding-bootcamp-1000-graduates/&quot;&gt;Le Wagon Tokyo campus reaches 1,000 graduates!&lt;/a&gt; est apparu en premier sur &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com&quot;&gt;Blog Le Wagon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 01:17:21 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Scaling smarter: Startup stories from Le Wagon Online Demo Day</title>
<link>https://blog.lewagon.com/news/scaling-smarter-startup-stories-from-le-wagon-online-demo-day/</link>
<description>&lt;p&gt;Missed the Growth Marketing online Demo Day? Discover how startups like Clay, Et Après, Moneycare, and Rotary are using marketing innovation to scale faster and smarter—with real case studies and videos.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;L’article &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com/news/scaling-smarter-startup-stories-from-le-wagon-online-demo-day/&quot;&gt;Scaling smarter: Startup stories from Le Wagon Online Demo Day&lt;/a&gt; est apparu en premier sur &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com&quot;&gt;Blog Le Wagon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 09:58:05 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Breaking Barriers: Women in AI – A panel discussion</title>
<link>https://blog.lewagon.com/news/breaking-barriers-women-in-ai-a-panel-discussion/</link>
<description>&lt;p&gt;Last fall, Le Wagon Montreal hosted a dynamic panel discussion on Women in AI, featuring Stefania Pecore – AI R&amp;#038;D Director and Ambassador for Women Techmakers, Women in AI, and Women in Games, and Gabrielle Hurtubise-Radet – Principal Manager of Startup Programs at Mila.&lt;br /&gt;
The discussion explored breaking barriers, navigating biases in AI, and empowering women to build careers in technology. The panelists shared personal experiences, insights, and practical advice for overcoming imposter syndrome and making an impact in AI.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;L’article &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com/news/breaking-barriers-women-in-ai-a-panel-discussion/&quot;&gt;Breaking Barriers: Women in AI – A panel discussion&lt;/a&gt; est apparu en premier sur &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com&quot;&gt;Blog Le Wagon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 21:15:53 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Growth Marketing Demo Day: showcasing innovation and impact</title>
<link>https://blog.lewagon.com/news/le-wagon-growth-marketing-bootcamp-demo-day/</link>
<description>&lt;p&gt;Le Wagon’s Growth Marketing Bootcamp Demo Day showcased innovative projects from our graduates, highlighting creativity, strategy, and real-world impact. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;L’article &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com/news/le-wagon-growth-marketing-bootcamp-demo-day/&quot;&gt;Growth Marketing Demo Day: showcasing innovation and impact&lt;/a&gt; est apparu en premier sur &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com&quot;&gt;Blog Le Wagon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 13:17:28 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>“Code, Baby, Code!” – Why Europe Must Invest in Developers to Leverage AI</title>
<link>https://blog.lewagon.com/news/code-baby-code-why-europe-must-invest-in-developers-to-leverage-ai/</link>
<description>&lt;p&gt;In the AI era, should entrepreneurs still invest in developers? In this article, Boris Paillard, Co-Founder and Executive Chairman of Le Wagon, breaks down why coding remains essential—even as No-Code and AI-powered tools evolve.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;L’article &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com/news/code-baby-code-why-europe-must-invest-in-developers-to-leverage-ai/&quot;&gt;&amp;#8220;Code, Baby, Code!&amp;#8221; &amp;#8211; Why Europe Must Invest in Developers to Leverage AI&lt;/a&gt; est apparu en premier sur &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com&quot;&gt;Blog Le Wagon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 10:23:42 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>The ultimate Learning Guide: How to prepare and thrive in a tech bootcamp</title>
<link>https://blog.lewagon.com/news/the-ultimate-learning-guide-how-to-prepare-and-thrive-in-a-tech-bootcamp/</link>
<description>&lt;p&gt;Is a bootcamp too intensive or complicated for you? Le Wagon’s learning guide gives you the answers and a clear roadmap to success. From preparation tips to career advice, discover what to expect and how to thrive. Download the full guide now!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;L’article &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com/news/the-ultimate-learning-guide-how-to-prepare-and-thrive-in-a-tech-bootcamp/&quot;&gt;The ultimate Learning Guide: How to prepare and thrive in a tech bootcamp&lt;/a&gt; est apparu en premier sur &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com&quot;&gt;Blog Le Wagon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 14:02:11 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Essential skills for the future of work: Insights from the Future of Jobs Report 2025</title>
<link>https://blog.lewagon.com/news/insights-from-the-future-of-jobs-report-2025/</link>
<description>&lt;p&gt;The World Economic Forum&#x27;s Future of Jobs Report 2025 highlights the skills shaping the future workforce. Analytical thinking, resilience, technological literacy, creative problem-solving, and leadership are essential for success in a rapidly evolving job market. With nearly 39% of current skills expected to become outdated by 2030, workers and employers must prioritize adaptability, upskilling, and lifelong learning. Discover how to prepare for the challenges and opportunities of the future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;L’article &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com/news/insights-from-the-future-of-jobs-report-2025/&quot;&gt;Essential skills for the future of work: Insights from the Future of Jobs Report 2025&lt;/a&gt; est apparu en premier sur &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com&quot;&gt;Blog Le Wagon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 10:33:52 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
