<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Le Wagon Career & Skills Selected Posts</title>
<link>https://blog.lewagon.com/</link>
<description>Custom RSS feed based on selected URLs</description>
<item>
<title>The Most In-Demand Tech & AI Skills in 2025</title>
<link>https://blog.lewagon.com/skills/the-most-in-demand-tech-ai-skills-in-2025/</link>
<description>&lt;p&gt;Discover the top tech and AI skills companies are hiring for in 2025, from generative AI and autonomous agents to real-time analytics and platform engineering. Stay ahead of the curve in a rapidly evolving job market.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;L’article &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com/skills/the-most-in-demand-tech-ai-skills-in-2025/&quot;&gt;The Most In-Demand Tech &#038; AI Skills in 2025&lt;/a&gt; est apparu en premier sur &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com&quot;&gt;Blog Le Wagon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 13:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>The beginner’s roadmap to rapid tech skill development</title>
<link>https://blog.lewagon.com/skills/the-beginners-roadmap-to-rapid-tech-skill-development/</link>
<description>&lt;p&gt;Master tech skills quickly with this beginner’s roadmap. Learn key skills, tools, and strategies to launch your tech career.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;L’article &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com/skills/the-beginners-roadmap-to-rapid-tech-skill-development/&quot;&gt;The beginner’s roadmap to rapid tech skill development&lt;/a&gt; est apparu en premier sur &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com&quot;&gt;Blog Le Wagon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 16:41:25 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>DevOps for beginners</title>
<link>https://blog.lewagon.com/skills/devops-for-beginners/</link>
<description>&lt;p&gt;DevOps is a collaborative approach that integrates software development (Dev) and IT operations (Ops) to streamline application delivery. By emphasizing automation, continuous integration, and continuous delivery, DevOps enhances software deployment speed, reliability, and quality. It fosters cross-functional collaboration, data-driven decisions, and continuous improvement, ensuring faster, more stable releases. This cultural shift helps organizations stay competitive, delivering high-quality software that meets customer needs and business goals efficiently. (Image source: GUVI Blog)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;L’article &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com/skills/devops-for-beginners/&quot;&gt;DevOps for beginners&lt;/a&gt; est apparu en premier sur &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com&quot;&gt;Blog Le Wagon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 15:51:36 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Diverse talent in tech: insights from Le Wagon’s job report</title>
<link>https://blog.lewagon.com/career/diverse-talent-in-tech-insights-from-le-wagons-job-report/</link>
<description>&lt;p&gt;You probably have some stereotypes about the tech industry, and we don&#x27;t blame you, most people do. For example, the tech world has been notorious for being a boys’ club. But our latest Online Job Report (2024) proves many of the common assumptions wrong. Spoiler: tech is finally starting to look like the real world!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;L’article &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com/career/diverse-talent-in-tech-insights-from-le-wagons-job-report/&quot;&gt;Diverse talent in tech: insights from Le Wagon’s job report&lt;/a&gt; est apparu en premier sur &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com&quot;&gt;Blog Le Wagon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 13:25:34 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Navigating the Tech Scene in the Netherlands: Insights from Our Careers Advisor</title>
<link>https://blog.lewagon.com/career/navigating-the-tech-scene-in-the-netherlands-insights-from-our-careers-advisor/</link>
<description>&lt;p&gt;The Dutch tech industry is a global leader in innovation, offering countless opportunities for those ready to dive in. To help you navigate this thriving landscape, we sat down with Harsh, one of our experienced careers advisors, to answer some key questions about the skills, sectors, and strategies that can help you succeed in the Netherlands.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;L’article &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com/career/navigating-the-tech-scene-in-the-netherlands-insights-from-our-careers-advisor/&quot;&gt;Navigating the Tech Scene in the Netherlands: Insights from Our Careers Advisor&lt;/a&gt; est apparu en premier sur &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com&quot;&gt;Blog Le Wagon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 10:51:26 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Navigating the Tech Scene in Belgium: Insights from Our Careers Advisor</title>
<link>https://blog.lewagon.com/career/navigating-the-tech-scene-in-belgium-insights-from-our-careers-advisor/</link>
<description>&lt;p&gt;The Belgian tech industry has amazing opportunities across a range of sectors. To help professionals gain clarity, we spoke with Harsh, one of our experienced careers advisors. He shared valuable insights about the skills, sectors, and strategies to find your dream job in tech.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;L’article &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com/career/navigating-the-tech-scene-in-belgium-insights-from-our-careers-advisor/&quot;&gt;Navigating the Tech Scene in Belgium: Insights from Our Careers Advisor&lt;/a&gt; est apparu en premier sur &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com&quot;&gt;Blog Le Wagon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 10:29:26 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Career Advice After a Bootcamp: Insights from Our Careers Advisor</title>
<link>https://blog.lewagon.com/career/career-advice-after-a-bootcamp-insights-from-our-careers-advisor/</link>
<description>&lt;p&gt;Graduating from a bootcamp is an exciting milestone, but the next steps can feel overwhelming. To help you navigate your journey into the tech world, our careers advisor Harsh answered some of the most common questions our graduates ask about preparing for interviews, standing out in a competitive market, and building a successful tech career.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;L’article &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com/career/career-advice-after-a-bootcamp-insights-from-our-careers-advisor/&quot;&gt;Career Advice After a Bootcamp: Insights from Our Careers Advisor&lt;/a&gt; est apparu en premier sur &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com&quot;&gt;Blog Le Wagon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 09:40:09 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>The tech freelancer’s playbook: Tips & tricks to succeed – part 2</title>
<link>https://blog.lewagon.com/career/the-tech-freelancers-playbook-tips-tricks-to-succeed-part-2/</link>
<description>&lt;p&gt;In this second part of an article series on freelancing, Audrey Gourdji, freelancer and Le Wagon alumna, explores the secrets to thriving as a tech freelancer, from building a standout portfolio to finding the right opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;L’article &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com/career/the-tech-freelancers-playbook-tips-tricks-to-succeed-part-2/&quot;&gt;The tech freelancer&#8217;s playbook: Tips &#038; tricks to succeed &#8211; part 2&lt;/a&gt; est apparu en premier sur &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com&quot;&gt;Blog Le Wagon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 15:10:57 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>The tech freelancer’s playbook: Getting started with solo tech work – part 1</title>
<link>https://blog.lewagon.com/career/the-tech-freelancers-playbook-getting-started-with-solo-tech-work-part-1/</link>
<description>&lt;p&gt;We had the opportunity to host Audrey Gourdji, who visited our Montreal campus to share her freelancing journey. She spoke about her experience transitioning from fashion to tech freelancing and provided practical insights for anyone considering a similar career shift. Based on the talk she gave, we offer this article series in 3 parts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;L’article &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com/career/the-tech-freelancers-playbook-getting-started-with-solo-tech-work-part-1/&quot;&gt;The tech freelancer&#8217;s playbook: Getting started with solo tech work &#8211; part 1&lt;/a&gt; est apparu en premier sur &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lewagon.com&quot;&gt;Blog Le Wagon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 19:21:09 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
